<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on flujoo</title>
    <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on flujoo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flujoo.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Approach to Automatic Musical Composition</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-approach-to-automatic-musical-composition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-approach-to-automatic-musical-composition/</guid>
      <description>In this blog, I will introduce my approach to automatic musical composition, including the theory, the algorithm, and a Python package implementation ch0p1n.
What Is Automatic Composition? Automatic composition is using algorithms to generate music.
As a trivial example, imagine that you put a cat on a piano to randomly press keys to generate music. The music is thus the result of a predetermined algorithm rather than of your instantaneous emotions or compositional skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Early Music</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-early-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-early-music/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my early compositions. Most of them are for practice purposes excerpt for the first one &amp;ldquo;Wind Is Ring&amp;rdquo;. The audio files are generated by MuseScore or Finale, so they may sound a little mechanical, although I tried to make them sound as natural as possible by carefully setting dynamics, pedals and tempos. Hope you can ignore the sound effect and enjoy the music.
&amp;ldquo;Wind Is Rising&amp;rdquo;  Score</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate Accompaniment Progression</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/generate-accompaniment-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/generate-accompaniment-progression/</guid>
      <description>Given a harmonic progression and the first accompaniment motif, how to automatically generate an entire accompaniment progression?
In this blog, I will tackle this problem with R language and R package &amp;ldquo;gm&amp;rdquo;. Please note that, for illustrative purposes, the solution presented here is only a simplified version. I will talk more about this in the last section.
Let&amp;rsquo;s first clarify the problem, before diving into it.
Clarify the Problem Take the beginning of Chopin&amp;rsquo;s nocturne Op.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Types of Music Analysis</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/three-types-of-music-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/three-types-of-music-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Music analysis is not a single method, framework, or theory; it has many different kinds. However, most kinds of music analysis can be put into the three categories I put forward in this blog.
Below I will talk about these three types of music analysis. And for illustrative purposes, I will use them to analyse Chopin&amp;rsquo;s nocturne Op.72 No.1. If you have not heard this nocturne yet, I highly recommend Maurizio Pollini&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Music Album &#34;Night&#34;</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-music-album-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-music-album-night/</guid>
      <description>Here is my first music album Night. It is a dark ambient album written for solo piano, which describes images and emotions related to night. This album has not been completed yet, so I present here only the first four works. The audio files are generated by Logic Pro.
Prelude Midnight  Score
It is midnight. The grandfather clock in the living room is ringing. You are transitioning from wakefulness to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
