<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on flujoo</title>
    <link>https://flujoo.github.io/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on flujoo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flujoo.github.io/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Generate Accompaniment Progression</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/generate-accompaniment-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/generate-accompaniment-progression/</guid>
      <description>Given a harmonic progression and the first accompaniment motif, how to automatically generate an entire accompaniment progression?
In this blog, I will tackle this problem with R language and R package &amp;ldquo;gm&amp;rdquo;. Please note that, for illustrative purposes, the solution presented here is only a simplified version. I will talk more about this in the last section.
Let&amp;rsquo;s first clarify the problem, before diving into it.
Clarify the Problem Take the beginning of Chopin&amp;rsquo;s nocturne Op.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Types of Music Analysis</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/three-types-of-music-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/three-types-of-music-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Music analysis is not a single method, framework, or theory; it has many different kinds. However, most kinds of music analysis can be put into the three categories I put forward in this blog.
Below I will talk about these three types of music analysis. And for illustrative purposes, I will use them to analyse Chopin&amp;rsquo;s nocturne Op.72 No.1. If you have not heard this nocturne yet, I highly recommend Maurizio Pollini&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Music Album &#34;Night&#34;</title>
      <link>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-music-album-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flujoo.github.io/en/my-music-album-night/</guid>
      <description>I have been working on my first music album &amp;ldquo;Night&amp;rdquo; recently. This is a dark ambient album, which describes images and emotions related to night. The whole album is written for solo piano, so if you would like to play any piece of it, send me an email to get the score.
This album is not fully completed yet. I am posting here only the first four pieces:
Prelude &amp;ldquo;Midnight&amp;rdquo;  Prelude &amp;ldquo;Moonlight&amp;rdquo;  Prelude &amp;amp; Fugue &amp;ldquo;Street after Rain&amp;rdquo;  Sonata &amp;ldquo;A Rainy Night&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
